<data>
	
	<brief>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[For contemporary ways of life in a new era, characterized by constant shifts and dynamic innovations, traditional means of communication remain impotent. Constructed in relation to established fields but defined in relation to current needs to come to terms with the rapid shifts in communication technologies, a new profession and a new field of study have emerged.<br><br>Visual Communication Design is never stable but always in the process of evolving in response to current demands of technology, society and culture. It is concerned with the transfer of information, by embedding digital technologies and traditional media in relation to each other, for which methodological thinking, creativity, theoretical knowledge and practical skills are all essentially required. Through design, our visual surroundings are analytically and creatively processed so as to be rendered persuasive, descriptive or informative.<br><br>Established in 1997, İstanbul Bilgi University Department of Visual Communication Design aims at educating the designers of tomorrow with the expertise to conceive the most compelling visual problems then dwell upon them systematically, applying their practical media skills together with theoretical knowledge so as to offer creative solutions. At the end of this challenging process, students become adept in advancing the applications of developing technologies in daily life. Towards the fulfilment of this mission, the program is designed to equip the students with a professional and comprehensive training in visual media while endowing them with the required intellectual skills. In VCD, the core courses cover various topics such as multimedia design, publication design, cyber culture, animation, typography and video production. The curriculum is shaped by the educational policy of the department which emphasizes production and the students are encouraged to develop their own personal style in design. Highly competitive student works are presented through annual exhibitions to the local audience and also find a chance to reach out to larger circles by participating in international festivals, as in the case of our exhibition at Ars Electronica Festival in 2005.<br><br>Driven by the ideal of design excellence, the department adopts a global understanding of design while setting its standards and is therefore involved in international collaborations, projects, student and instructor exchange programs through its membership of several international associations.]]>
		</plain>
	</brief>
	
	<admissions>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[VCD (Visual Communication Design) and POV (Photography and Video) Departments accept students through an Aptitude Exam.<br>The Aptitude Exam is held in August each year by İstanbul Bilgi University VCD and POV Departments. Announcements can be found in advance at İstanbul Bilgi University’s and VCD and POV Departments’ web sites as early as July.<br>The Aptitude Test is held jointly by VCD and POV Departments. However, applicants are expected to determine which department they will be applying to before the Test. Applicants can also apply to both departments by declaring the preferred and the secondary choice. The jury may invite an applicant to the non-preferred department according to the results of the exam and the portfolio evaluation even if he/she had opted for only one department.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Examination Process and Application with or without Scholarship]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[There are two ways of applying to the VCD and POV Departments: with or without scholarship.<br>Candidates applying without a scholarship request will be subject to an examination process of three steps: a multiple choice test of 100 questions, an applied creativity examination and a short interview. VCD and/or POV student candidates applying with a scholarship request are expected to take an additional applied examination.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Multiple Choice Test]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[The test, which is comprised of 100 questions, is the first step of the Aptitude Examination. The test covers areas such as music, cinema, computers, internet, contemporary art as well as visual culture and visual perception. Questions about visual culture involves images from media we constantly encounter in our daily lives such as billboards, posters, banners, logos, etc. Questions about visual perception deal with shape completion, interrelations between shapes and three dimensional visualization skills. The duration of the test, where wrong answers do not reduce the correct answer count, is 90 minutes. Applicants who fail this test lose the opportunity to study in the departments.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Applied Creativity Examination]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Student candidates take the Applied Creativity Examination immediately after the Multiple Choice Test, without waiting for the announcement of the results. In other words, all applicants are subject to this examination as well. During the examination, applicants are expected to create a design solution with a personal approach according to the given instructions, using the limited material provided. This examination is to some extent based on handcraft. Works produced are later evaluated by the jury regarding criteria such as creativity, genuineness and ability to take risks. Works created by student candidates who failed at the test are disregarded.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Additional Applied Examination for Candidates with a Scholarship Request]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[This step of the Aptitude Examination is required only for VCD and/or POV student candidates applying with a scholarship request.<br>The applied examination for VCD student candidates applying for a scholarship is carried out in the departments’ computer labs. Applicants are expected to create a series of design products according to a given brief, within a time limit. Computers used are equipped in advance with relevant software and visual materials required.<br>POV student candidates applying for a scholarship on the other hand shoot photographs / video footage according to a subject / concept announced at the start of the examination. Necessary equipment is provided by the department. Applicants are expected to submit images / footage after working within a time limit at designated locations.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Interview]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Candidates scoring above the threshold grade at the Multiple Choice Test and fulfilling the requirements of the applied examination(s) are invited to the final step which is the interview. Interviews are organized in order to get to know student candidates better and evaluate their portfolio if any by the exam jury which consists of VCD and POV Departments’ instructors. In this face to face meeting, applicants get the opportunity to introduce and express themselves and explain why they wish to join the program they applied for.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Who Can Apply]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Candidates who obtain base score or higher in any kind of composite scores (Weighted Quantitative Composite 1, Weighted Verbal Composite 1, V-Q Equally Weighted Composite 1) at the Student Selection Examination (ÖSS) are allowed to apply to the Aptitude Examination organized by the Visual Communication Design and Photography & Video Departments. Required legal documentation for applications is as listed below:]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Application Form]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Application forms can be accessed at <a href="http://www.bilgi.edu.tr"></a>www.bilgi.edu.tr</a> after the announcement of the examination dates. Candidates must fill, print out and submit the preregistration forms which can also be accessed from computers reserved for candidates at İstanbul Bilgi University santralistanbul Campus, Communication and Counseling Unit.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Student Selection Examination (ÖSS) Score Report]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Original or photocopy of the official score report posted by the Student Selection and Placement Center (ÖSYM) is required.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Preregistration Fees Receipt]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Candidates must pay the preregistration fee specified in the announcements to İstanbul Bilgi University Communication and Counseling Unit at santralistanbul Campus and keep the receipt in order to complete the preregistration.]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[2 ID photographs]]>
		</h3>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Photocopy of ID Card]]>
		</h3>
		<h2break></h2break>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Candidates must submit the completed and signed application form, preregistration fee receipt, ÖSS score report, 2 ID photographs and photocopy of national identity card to İstanbul Bilgi University Communication and Counseling Unit at santralistanbul Campus, have their application certified and receive their examination entrance document.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Portfolio]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[The portfolio is a compilation of personal works related to the department which is applied to, demonstrating the progress and achievements carried out by the candidate. The portfolio prepared for VCD and/or POV Departments is expected to contain applicants’ personal projects related to the preferred department(s). The candidate students are expected to be careful and organized in the selection of the content and instead of creating a pile of all the works formerly realized, they are recommended to prepare a portfolio containing selected works. This selection is expected to contain professional, semi-professional or amateur works such as photographs, music videos, short films, posters, invitation cards, web pages etc. Applicants must clearly specify their functions in group works if included in the portfolio. As VCD and POV Departments’ educational structure is based on computer skills, handcrafted works such as sketches and drawings are not recommended and will be disregarded if included. A portfolio is only mandatory for candidates applying with a scholarship request. However all applicants are recommended to submit their existing works as this will improve their interview performance. Portfolios should be prepared as a CD or DVD and must be personally submitted to VCD and POV Departments’ teaching assistants within the dates specified for the examination application. Please note that the portfolios will not be returned.]]>
		</plain>
	</admissions>
	
	<scholarships>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Each year, İstanbul Bilgi University VCD and POV Departments grant 10 candidates full scholarships. According to the results of the exam process, among candidates applying for a scholarship, 5 best scoring students for each department will receive full scholarships. In return of the scholarships, students are obliged to work for the departments. Commitments of students granted with a full scholarship are as listed below:<br><br>1. Student’s annual GPA must be at least 2.75 out of 4.<br>2. Students are expected to work for the departments’ events and projects as:<br>- Designer<br>- Software developer<br>- Organization activities assistant<br>- Archival operations assistant<br>- Photography and video works assistant<br>- Promotional activities assistant<br><br>At the end of each year, Visual Communication Design Department’s Scholarship Committee evaluate the scholarships given regarding these conditions. The evaluation considers the students’ annual GPA and efficiency to fulfill the commitments regarding the department’s activities. As a result of the evaluation, scholarships of students who do not fulfill the commitments are discontinued and, after a new evaluation, the scholarship is granted to other students who had earlier applied for a scholarship, but had scored below the first five.<br>At the registration phase of the Aptitude Examination, candidates applying for a scholarship sign a written engagement indicating that they accept the criteria and commitments defined above.]]>
		</plain>
	</scholarships>
	
	<leaflet>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[2008-2009 Undergraduate and Graduate Leaflets cover information about the academic staff and curricula of Istanbul Bilgi University; Visual Communication Design, Photography and Video, Film and Television Departments.]]>
		</plain>
		<linkbutton>
			<label>
				<![CDATA[Leaflet (2.125KB)]]>
			</label>
			<src>
				<![CDATA[Files/Leaflet.zip]]>
			</src>
		</linkbutton>
	</leaflet>
	
	<presskit>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[The Press Kit comprises a selection of student works, campus photographs and VCD, POV, FTV Departments' logos.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Student Works]]>
		</h2>
		<linkbutton>
			<label>
				<![CDATA[Student_Works.zip (23.840KB)]]>
			</label>
			<src>
				<![CDATA[Files/Student_Works.zip]]>
			</src>
		</linkbutton>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Campus Photographs]]>
		</h2>
		<linkbutton>
			<label>
				<![CDATA[E1SantralPhotos.zip (78.440KB)]]>
			</label>
			<src>
				<![CDATA[Files/E1SantralPhotos.zip]]>
			</src>
		</linkbutton>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[VCD, FTV, POV Department Logos]]>
		</h2>
		<linkbutton>
			<label>
				<![CDATA[Logos.zip (2.540KB)]]>
			</label>
			<src>
				<![CDATA[Files/Logos.zip]]>
			</src>
		</linkbutton>
	</presskit>
	
</data>