<data>
	
	<international>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[International Contacts and Exchange]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[In accordance with the needs of modern education, Departments of Visual Communication Design (VCD) and Photography & Video (POV) give high priority to international engagement. This involvement takes place on three core areas, the first one covers the departments' membership to various international networks, second is the exchange programmes and the third is the participation to international festivals and events.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Cumulus Membership]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[VCD and POV Departments have become a member of CUMULUS (International Association of Universities and Colleges of Art, Design and Media) as of June, 2006. For further information on CUMULUS, please visit<br><a href="hrrp://www.cumulusassociation.org">www.cumulusassociation.org</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Icograda Membership]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[VCD and POV Departments are members of Icograda (International Council of Graphic Design Associations).<br>For further information on Icograda, please visit<br><a href="http://www.education.icograda.net">www.education.icograda.net</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[International Exchange]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[In accordance with the needs of modern education, the departments of Visual Communication Design (VCD), Film and Television (FTV) and Photography & Video (POV) give high priority to international engagement. This involvement takes place in three core areas. The first one covers the departments' membership to various international networks; the second is the exchange programs and the third is participation in international festivals and events. The current international student and instructor exchanges take place within the scope of the Erasmus Program and other bilateral exchange agreements. Through the Erasmus agreements signed with 16 universities in Europe, VCD, FTV and POV Departments provide their students with the opportunity to spend part of their study abroad and present the visiting students with the unique chance of partaking in the welcoming and vibrant academic environment at BİLGİ.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[What Is Erasmus?]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[The Erasmus Program was established by the European Union to enhance quality in and reinforce the European dimension of higher education, by encouraging transnational cooperation between universities. The Erasmus Program in particular, is designed to foster student and teaching staff mobility in Europe.<br>İstanbul Bilgi University began to participate in the Erasmus Program during the 2004-2005 academic year. BİLGİ provides its students with an opportunity to live and study in Europe in order to broaden their educational and cultural horizons under the framework of the Erasmus Program. For this purpose, many BİLGİ departments have established Erasmus partnerships with their counterparts, at numerous distinguished European universities. Students who participate in the Erasmus Program may spend between three months and a full academic year abroad at BİLGİ’s partner universities. Erasmus students may benefit from EU mobility grants.<br>Undergraduate students must have completed one full year of their academic Program at BİLGİ before applying for an exchange. Students must return to their home universities at the end of the exchange period and complete their Program of study at their home university. Credits obtained from the partner university are applied towards graduation at BİLGİ, subject to the approval of relevant BİLGİ units.<br>The Erasmus Program at BİLGİ is managed by the International Office at the institutional level.  The International Office is responsible for the announcements, applications, selection of students, mobility grants etc. Also every BİLGİ department has an Erasmus coordinator, responsible for academic advising and the agreements of the department.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Application For Erasmus Program]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Eligibility Criteria:<br>- Successful completion of the first year of the degree Program.<br>- Minimum GPA of 2.0 for undergraduate, 2.5 for graduate students.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Application Procedures]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Students should apply to the International Office with the documents listed below:<br>- Application Form. (<a href="http://studyabroad.bilgi.edu.tr/docs/Study_Abroad_Form.doc">http://studyabroad.bilgi.edu.tr/docs/Study_Abroad_Form.doc</a>)<br>- Letter of Intent in English, explaining why you want to participate in the exchange Program, why you would be a suitable candidate, where you want to go and why.<br>- CV in English.<br>- Transcript of Records. (student copy)]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[Important Dates]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[20 February 2009<br>The deadline for applications to undertake an Erasmus exchange study during the 2009-2010 academic year.<br>02-20 March 2009<br>Selection of students for exchange during the 2009-2010 academic year.]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[For Further Information]]>
		</h2>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[İstanbul Bilgi University International Office]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Phone: 0 212 311 51 17- 0 212 311 52 17<br>Fax: 0 212 253 47 02<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:intl@bilgi.edu.tr">intl@bilgi.edu.tr</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[VCD and POV Departments Erasmus Coordinator]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Ali Pekşen<br>Phone:0 212 311 75 13<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:ali@vcd.bilgi.edu.tr">ali@vcd.bilgi.edu.tr</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[FTV Department Erasmus Coordinator]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Dirk Schaefer<br>Phone: 0 212 311 75 17<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:dschaefer@bilgi.edu.tr">dschaefer@bilgi.edu.tr</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[2009-2010 Erasmus Partners]]>
		</h2>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Vorarlberg University of Applied Sciences (Austria)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Media Design<br><a href="http://www.fh-vorarlberg.ac.at">www.fh-vorarlberg.ac.at</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Upper Austria University of Applied Sciences, Hagenberg (Austria)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Media<br>Technology and Design<br>Department of Digital Media<br><a href="http://www.fh-hagenberg.at">www.fh-hagenberg.at</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Salzburg University of Applied Sciences (Austria)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Multimedia Art<br>Department of Digital TV<br><a href="http://www.fh-salzburg.ac.at">www.fh-salzburg.ac.at</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[University of Art and Design Helsinki (Finland)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Media Lab<br>Department of Design<br>Department of Visual Culture<br>Department of New Media<br><a href="http://taik.fi/">www.taik.fi</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Munich University of Plastic Arts (Germany)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Fine and Applied Arts<br>Department of Painting and Graphics Art<br><a href="http://www.adbk.mhn.de">www.adbk.mhn.de</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Aristotle University of Thessaloniki (Greece)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Photography<br><a href="http://www.auth.gr">www.auth.gr</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Free University of Bozen-Bolzano (Italy)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Art and Design<br><a href="http://www.unibz.it/design-art">www.unibz.it/design-art</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Academy of Fine Arts of Brera –Milano( Italy)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Art and Design<br><a href="http://www.accademiadibrera.milano.it">www.accademiadibrera.milano.it</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Art University Linz (Austria)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Art and Design<br><a href="http://www.ufg.ac.at">www.ufg.ac.at</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[University of Applied Sciences Augsburg (Germany )]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Communication Design<br>Department of Interactive Media<br><a href="http://www.fh-augsburg.de">www.fh-augsburg.de</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[University of Art and Design Lausanne (Switzerland)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Media<br>Department of Interaction Design<br><a href="http://www.ecal.ch">www.ecal.ch</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h3>
			<![CDATA[Sint-Lucas Art College, Gent (Belgium)]]>
		</h3>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[Department of Visual Design<br>Department of Visual Art<br><a href="http://www.kunst.sintlucas.wenk.be/">www.kunst.sintlucas.wenk.be</a>]]>
		</plain>
		<h2>
			<![CDATA[International Festivals]]>
		</h2>
		<plain>
			<![CDATA[The creativeness, innovation, technical and theoretical competence that our students' works prove, attracted various renowned international festivals and events. Departments of Visual Communication Design (VCD) and Photography & Video (POV) have so far been invited to the following festivals and events with its highly competitive students' works.<br><br>2005<br>Ars Electronica 2005 (Festival for Art, Technology and Society)<br><a href="http://www.aec.at/de/festival2005/programm/project.asp?iProjectID=13075">www.aec.at/de/festival2005/programm/project.asp?iProjectID=13075</a><br><br>2006<br>Premiers Plans Film Festival<br><a href="http://www.premiersplans.org/">www.premiersplans.org/</a><br><br>Festival Némo<br><a href="http://www.arcadi.fr/telechargements/nemo_2006.pdf">www.arcadi.fr/telechargements/nemo_2006.pdf</a><br><br>Cumulus EWOL (European Ways of Life)<br><a href="http://www.cumulus-ewol.org/index.php?r=5&p=6&l=en">www.cumulus-ewol.org/index.php?r=5&p=6&l=en</a><br><br>VIDEONET-06<br><a href="http://www.uem.es/esaya/videonet/#VIDEONET-06">www.uem.es/esaya/videonet/#VIDEONET-06</a>]]>
		</plain>
	</international>
	
</data>